

INFORMATION

Date of birth: 19.08.2002

Adress: Norre Havnegade 40,2,-37

6400 Sonderborg

E-mail: krzys.orczykagmail.com Phone: +48 600 559 152 Polish Phone: +45 55 20 88 76 Danish

Courses

- CNC machine tools course 23.05.2021
- SPACE BGA ESC/REF 2020 soldering course
- Certified IPC Specialist 7711/7721 25.02.2020
- Routers and switches service course Cisco 12.05.2021
- SEP to G-1E with exam 24.09.2021
- Wizzair (Navitaire) Departure system

FOREIGN LANGUAGES

English - Fluent Polish - First Language

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Volunteer in a student bar at SDU as a bartender

Hobby

- Glider Pilot
- Scuba Diving on PADI license OWD
- Inshore Skipper on ISSA license
- Electronics
- Programming
- 3D modeling

Krzysztof Orczyk

Career Summary

I'm a second-year electronic engineering student at SDU with experience in the assembly of electrical and electronic installations, IT support and Programing.

Having numerous professional qualifications related to the operation of electrical devices, network administration and configuration of computer equipment.

Highly developed interpersonal skills, efficient adaptation to the new environment, proactive attitude focused on searching for innovative solutions.

Work experiences

Bartender, Waiter, Kitchen Helper

April 2023 - November 2023

RESTAURANT COLOSSEUM Served bar and restaurant patrons ordered drinks, including beer, wine, liquors, and mixed beverages.

- Kept the bar area safe, clean, and well-stocked throughout each working
- Took orders for drinks from local quests and delivered them accurately and promptly.

Pax Agent

June 2022 - September 2022

- LS AIRPORT SERVICES assisting ticketed passengers during check-in, helping them check luggage and print boarding passes, and ensuring that they have proper documentation to board the plane or
 - Boarding passengers at gate

ODERON

IT SUPPORT

apprenticeship. May 2021 - 2023

- Assembly, installation and technical support for servers
- Service desk
- Accumulation of experience, Building an internet network of an Installation of surveillance cameras ophthalmic hospital
 - Programming in C#, C, Java, Python
 - SQL server

Education

HIGH SCHOOL

Electronics technician specialization

September 2018 -April 2022

UNIVERSITY

Bachelor engineering in electronics

- 2 year

September 2022 - now

Professional competence

- Technical ability
- Interpersonal skills
- Adaptability
- Logical and critical thinking
- Flexibility and creativity
- hard-working
- Resistance to stress
- Ability to work in a team
- Good manners
- Diligence and willingness to develop
- well-organised